菲比  快看窗边那个男的
Phoebe. Will you check out that guy by the window.
他矮得出奇
He's awfully short.
而且我觉得他在自言自语
And I think he's talking to himself.
老实说  他的床上功夫不怎么样
And to be completely honest, he's not that good in bed.
我最近是怎么了
What is wrong with me lately?
我对看到的每个男人都心动
It's like, every guy I see.
譬如说那个男的
I mean, look at that guy, for example.
他不是我喜欢的那一型
That's not someone I would be attracted to.
但凭我现在的感觉
But right now, with the way I'm feeling,
我一心想撕开他的运动裤跟腰包
all I want to do is rip off his sweatpants and fanny pack.
等一下
Wait a second!
你怀孕大概四个月了吧
This is about the fourth month of your pregnancy, right?
对  这再正常不过了
Yeah.  This is completely normal.
怀孕四个月时  你的荷尔蒙分泌会失控
Around the fourth month, your hormones start going crazy.
真的吗  你当时也是这样吗  没错
Really? So this has happened to you?  Absolutely! Yeah.
别忘了我怀的是三胞胎
And keep in mind now, I was carrying triplets.
从医学上来说  我的欲望要比你强三倍
So in medical terms, I was thrice as randy.
原来是这么一回事
Wow, this explains so much!
上周末我走遍每一家商店
Last weekend, I went from store to store,
坐在圣诞老人的大腿上
sitting on Santas' laps.
对  我记得我当时想要从健身房
Yeah, I remember trying to steal a cardboard cutout...
偷走艾凡德·霍利菲尔德的人形立牌
...of Evander Holyfield from a Foot Locker.
明天我得去看医生  我到时问问她
Well, I go see my doctor tomorrow. I'll ask her about this.
或许她可以开个药给我吃
Maybe she can give me a pill or something.
对  你正是需要吃药  对症"下药"
Yeah, that's what you need. A good pill.
《老友记》  第八季  第11集  罗斯向前跨了一大步
Friends S08E11 The One With Ross'Big Step Forward
我把我们到洛克菲勒中心的照片洗出来了
I got our pictures developed from Rockefeller Center.
太棒了  乔伊  你想看我跟蒙娜
Great. Hey, Joey, want to check out pictures
去溜冰的照片吗
of me and Mona iceskating?
换做平常我会想看
Ordinarily, I would love to,
但现在我真的好忙
but I am just swamped right now.
那个怪怪的咸酥饼小贩
Where are the pictures that
帮我们合拍的照片在哪里
that creepy pretzel vendor took of us together?
对  或许在最后面
Oh, yeah. Probably at the end.
天啊  他只拍了我的胸部
Oh, my God! All he took were pictures of my breasts.
我也想看照片
I'm missing picture time!
她长得也不错耶  罗斯
You know, she has a face, Ross.
我们这张合照很不错
Okay, here's a good one of us.
这张真的很棒  看起来很像节日贺卡
Wow, that is a good one! It looks like a holiday card.
中间有树  还有溜冰客和雪
With the tree in the middle and the skaters and the snow.
每年我都说要寄节日贺卡
Every year, I say I'm gonna send out
但从来都没着手去做
holiday cards and I never do it.
你要跟我一起寄这张卡片吗
Do you want to send this one out together?
一起寄我们的合照给大家
Together? Like, to people?
对  "佳节愉快  蒙娜跟罗斯上"
Yeah. "Happy holidays, from Mona and Ross."
一定会很棒  对吧
It'll be cute, okay?
好吧
Okay.
我得去上班了
I gotta get to work.
待会打电话给我  没问题
Call me later?  Sure, sure.
大家再见  再见
Bye, guys.  Bye.
恭喜  你刚刚结婚了
Congratulations! You just got married!
我知道  你敢相信吗
I know. Can you believe that?
抱歉  一张贺卡有什么大不了的
I'm sorry. What's the big deal about a holiday card?
已婚夫妻跟家人才会一起寄照片
Married couples send out cards. Families send out cards.
约会了几个月的情侣
People who have been dating for a couple of months
不会一起寄卡片
don't send out cards.
她疯了吗
What is she, crazy?
你说的人可是你老婆
That's your wife you're talking about!
宾  还有宾太太
Bing! And the Bingette!
老婆  你记得我老板道格吧  记得
Oh, honey, you remember my boss, Doug.  Yes. Hi.
好消息  我已经离婚了
Hi. So, good news! The divorce is final.
我今天早上签了文件
I signed the papers this a.m.
我不知道你跟卡拉离婚了  我很遗憾
I didn't know you and Kara divorced. I'm sorry.
遗憾  我终于可以脱离苦海了
Sorry? I finally chewed my leg out of that bear trap.
不过还是恭喜你们
Congratulations to you guys, though.
我们感情好着呢
No legchewing for us, sir.
等着瞧吧
Well, give it time.
你们刚结婚  我刚离婚  该好好庆祝一番
So the divorce, the marriage, we got a lot to celebrate.
我们何不明晚一起吃晚餐
How about we all go out to dinner tomorrow night.
我想不出来我们明晚要做什么事
I can't think of anything we're doing.
为什么我想不出来我们明晚要做什么事
Why can't I think of anything we're doing?
那就定在明晚  我六点应该能离开法庭
Tomorrow night it is. I should be out of court by 6.
他们一直拿性骚扰案扔给我
They keep throwing sexual harassment cases at me...
我总能把他们打得毫无退路
...and I keep knocking them out of the park!
好吧  明天见
Okay, see you tomorrow.
你要知道  我们明天不能跟他见面
Just so you know, we're not seeing him tomorrow.
我没办法再跟他共度一个夜晚
I can't spend another evening with that man.
你记得他在我们的婚礼上做了什么吗
Do you remember how he behaved at our wedding?
不记得  那是因为我们没有邀请他
No.  That's because he wasn't invited.
因为他在我们的订婚派对上为非作歹
Because of the way he behaved at our engagement party.
对  小便直接喷中了冰雕  对吧
Oh, yeah! Urine cuts right through an ice sculpture, doesn't it?
我去过照相馆了  你看
Hi! I went by the photo shop. Take a look.
这是卡片的初稿  你觉得怎样
Here is a mockup of our card. What do you think?
真的很棒
Wow, that's great.
你觉得我们该写上"爱你们的罗斯跟蒙娜"吗
Do you think it should say, "Love, Ross and Mona"?
我们还没有对彼此说过"爱"
Well, we haven't said that to each other yet...
但我猜跟其他人说说应该没关系
...but I guess it's okay to say it to other people.
你要多少张
How many did you want?
我要100张  100张
I'll get 100. A hundred?
那我就要...
Well, I guess I'll take...
蒙娜
Mona?
我不确定印卡片这件事妥不妥
I'm not sure about the whole card thing.
真的吗  为什么
Really? Why not?
我们一起寄节日贺卡
Sending out a holiday card together?
我不知道我们之间是不是到那个地步了
I just don't know if we're really quite there yet.
我没想到那一点  你说得对
I didn't think of it that way. You're right. You're right.
我能问你一个问题吗  好啊
So can I ask you a question?  Yeah.
我们到哪个地步了
Where are we?
You know, like where are we?
我们会有什么结局
Where is this relationship going?
我喜欢跟你待在一起
I mean, I love spending time with you.
我只是希望我们在往前走
I just hope we're moving forward.
我们该谈一谈  你不觉得吗
We should talk about that, don't you think?
我们一起印卡片吧
Let's do the card!
什么  卡片  我想我们到这个地步了
What?  The card! I think we're there!
好吧  但我还是觉得我们应该谈一谈
Okay. But I still think we should have this conversation.
真的吗
Really? I mean...
印了卡片还是要谈吗
Even with the card?
朗医生今天没办法过来
Just so you know, Dr. Long can't be here today,
她有事去医院了  辛夫医生会帮你检查
she was called to the hospital, so Dr. Schiff will be seeing you.
好吧  我能问你一个问题吗
Oh, okay. Can I ask you a question?
是我的问题  还是帮我抽血的那个家伙
Was it me, or was the guy who took my blood sample
真的很帅
really cute?
你知道我在说谁吗
You know who I'm talking about?
锅盖头  手指满是毛的家伙
Bowl haircut, hairy fingers?
瑞秋吗  我是辛夫医生  是啊
Hi, Rachel? I'm Dr. Schiff.  Yes, you are.
情况如何
So, how's it going?
真的很不错  但别谈我了
It's going really good. But enough about me! Come on.
你是哪里人  你是做哪一行的
Where are you from? What do you do?
我是医生  对  我是指...
I'm a doctor.  Right. I meant...
你有空的时候  你会煮饭或滑雪吗
...in your spare time. Do you cook? So you ski?
还是会跟太太或女朋友一起出去玩
Or just hang out with your wife, or girlfriend?
我没有太太或女朋友  但我很喜欢滑雪
I don't have a wife or a girlfriend, but I do like to ski.
我也喜欢滑雪  我们简直太有缘了
I love to ski! How amazing is this?
你最近有任何不适症状吗
Are you experiencing any discomfort?
不  我非常舒服
No, I'm very comfortable.
放屁会不舒服吗  不会
Any painful gas?  No!
辛夫医生  那是哪门子的问题
No! Shoot, Dr. Schiff! What kind of question is that?
好吧  能麻烦你躺下来吗
Okay, then. Would you like to lie down on the table?
你想让我躺下来吗
Would you like me to lie down on the table?
抱歉  我们之间是不是有什么情况
I'm sorry. Is there something going on here?
你也感觉到了吗
Do you feel it too?
门诊看得如何
So, how did your doctor's appointment go?
让我想一想
Well, let's see,
今天他们派了一个"帅哥"医生给我
they gave me "cute boy" doctor today.
检查到一半  我把小指放到他的下巴酒窝里了
In the middle of the exam, I put my pinkie in his chin dimple.
天啊  你为什么要那么做
Oh, my God!  Why did you do that?
还记得我怀孕四个月时
Remember that little problem
遇到的那个小问题吗
I was having during my fourth month of pregnancy?
对  艾凡德·霍利菲尔德的人形立牌
Oh, yeah! The Evander Holyfield phase.
天啊  你当时病急乱投医  甚至朝我扑过来
Oh, man! You were so hard up, you practically came on to me.
少做梦了
You wish.
如果我真的想要你  完全可以钓到你
Hey, I could have had you if I wanted you.
是吗  来试试看吧
Oh, yeah? Come and get it.
好了  连这段对话都能挑起我的欲望
Okay, even this is turning me on...
罗斯
Hey, Ross!
你跟蒙娜还好吧
How's it going with you and Mona?
你们还在一起吗
Are you guys still together?
对  我们有所进展  你们会收到我们的卡片
Yeah, we're moving forward. You'll be getting our card.
你们要一起寄节日贺卡吗
You're doing a holiday card together?
我们不只要寄节日贺卡
We're not just doing a card.
她还要谈一谈
She also wants to have the conversation...
我们会有什么结局
...about where the relationship is going.
女人啊
Women!
就是嘛  为什么你们想要谈这种问题
I know! Why do you guys need to have this conversation?
懂得自我尊重的男人不会问女人
No selfrespecting man would ask a woman,
"我们会有什么结局"
"So where is this going?"
罗斯  你问过我
Ross, you asked me that.
你像是本合上的书  好吗
You were a closed book, okay?
我又不会读心术
I'm not a mind reader!
而且我讨厌谈那种话题
Besides, I hate those conversations.
我真的不大会应付那种对话
I'm horrible at them. Really.
或许我需要暗示她
Maybe I need some kind of a gesture...
我们的确有进展
...something that says we're moving forward
而不必去谈这件事
without having to talk about it.
像是请她搬去跟你一起住
Like asking her to move in with you?
这有点过了
Smaller than that.
帮她录集锦录音带  又欠点火候
Making her a mix tape?  Bigger than that.
给她你家的钥匙
Give her a key to your apartment.
我们的感情还是更接近送录音带的程度
Hello. We were closer with the mix tape.
你说过"我爱你"吗  你可以说"我爱你"
Have you said, "I love you"? You could say, "I love you."
我觉得我还没有到那个地步
I don't think I'm quite there yet.
但我可以说"我喜欢跟你在一起"
But I could say, "I love spending time with you."
我们讨厌那句话
We hate that.
简直就像是被人闪了一巴掌
That is a slap in the face.
算了  我还是去跟她谈吧
Forget it. You know what? I'll just have the conversation.
我会说我喜欢我们现在的样子
I'll just say I like things the way they are,
并怀着最好的期待
and hope for the best.
你觉得呢  瑞秋
What do you think, Rach?
我想如果这里再冷一点
I think if it was a little colder in here...
我可以看到你乳头凸显
...I could see your nipples through that sweater.
宾  我们今晚八点出发
Bing? We're all set for tonight, 8:00.
我们去不成了  莫妮卡得上班
As it turns out, we can't do it. Monica has to work.
我前妻不上班
My exwife didn't work.
除非你说回娘家是"上班"
Unless you call turning into her mother "work."
好吧  那就明天晚上吧
Fine. Tomorrow night then.
她明晚也不能来  为什么
Tomorrow's no good for her, either.  Why not?
草地保龄球巡回赛
It's the semifinals...
要打半决赛
...of her bocce ball tournament.
发生了什么事  宾
What's going on, Bing?
你老婆不喜欢我吗
Does your wife have a problem with me or something?
你这话说得太离谱了
Well, now you're just talking crazy.
那我们三个为什么不能一起出去玩
Then why can't the three of us go out together?
因为我们分居了
Because we split up.
莫妮卡跟我分居了
Monica and I split up.
抱着我
Hold me.
天啊  宾  我倒也不觉得诧异
Good God, Bing. Well, I can't say I'm altogether surprised.
我看到她看你的眼神  就知道她不爱你
I saw the way she looked at you, and there was no love there.
而她看着我时却充满了爱欲
And the way she looked at me, pure lust.
在这种时候  只有掐人脖子
What would really help me through this tough time
才能让我泄愤  我能掐你吗
is choking someone. Can I choke you?
宾  孩子  我得让你放下这件事
Bing, my boy, we're gonna get you over this.
我有个计划
Here's the plan:
拿着你的外套  我们去脱衣舞俱乐部
Grab your coat, we're going to a strip club!
不  莫妮卡会生气的
Oh, no! Monica would freak.
但谁管那个臭女人呢
But to hell with that bitch!
咖啡来了
Here we go.
蒙娜  我们该谈谈
Mona, it's time we had a conversation
我们之间的关系了
about where things are with us.
是啊  那还是我先提出来的
Yeah, I think I suggested that.
我们简直...
We are so...
我真的很喜欢你
Well, I really like you.
我喜欢跟你在一起
And I love hanging out with you.
和你相处  我非常开心
And I'm having a lot of fun.
好吧
Okay.
如果只是为了好玩  我们就不必交往了
There's no point in spending time with someone if it's just fun.
我们得有结果  对吧
It's gotta be going somewhere, right?
我们会有什么结果
So where is it going?
这才是实质性的问题
That's the real question.
答案是...
And the answer is...
我们会相处得...
...it's going somewhere...
很开心
...fun.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
如果是十年前  还可以找找乐子
Fun was fine for you 10 years ago.
但现在你也不年轻了
But you're not getting any younger.
我不是说你  不是你
No! I mean, not you. Not you.
你越来越年轻了
You are getting younger!
你每一秒都在变年轻
You're getting younger by the second.
你有什么秘诀
What's your secret?
抱歉  我们发展到哪一步了
I'm sorry, so where are we?
总而言之...
Well, to sum up...
我们相处得很开心
...we're having fun.
你看起来很年轻
You look young.
好吧...  但这还远远不够
Okay...  But that's not enough.
所以...
So...
这是我家的钥匙
...here's a key to my apartment.
真的吗  真的
Really?  Really.
你不觉得发展得太快了吗
You don't think this is too fast?
你给了她你家的钥匙
You gave her a key to your apartment?
不仅是那样  我把唯一的钥匙给了她
Not just a key. I gave her the only key!
我现在是个陷入认真感情  无家可归的家伙
I am now a homeless person in a very serious relationship!
罗斯  你们谈得如何
Ross, how did the conversation go?
很棒  我现在流落街头了
Great. I live on the street.
哪里
Where?
好吧  莫妮卡  瑞秋...
Okay, Monica, Rachel...
他是我朋友罗杰  嗨  罗杰
...this is my friend Roger.  Hi, Roger.
罗杰
Hi, Roger.
我去拿饮料  你能过来帮我吗
I'll get us some drinks. Could you help me out?
好吧
Yeah, okay.
他是来跟你做爱的
He's here to have sex with you.
什么  别客气
What?  You're welcome.
菲比  不  没关系  他是个处男
Phoebe, no!  It's okay. He's a virgin.
瑞秋  我跟这个家伙聊天
Rachel, I was talking to this guy.
我觉得他要跟你做爱
I think he'll have sex with you.
让他们两个独处一下吧
Let's leave these two alone.
不要  不管我的荷尔蒙怎么作祟
No! I don't care what my hormones are doing!
我不会随便跟男人上床
I won't do it with some random guy!
好吧  那么你去告诉罗杰
Fine! Then you tell Roger,
因为他真的很期待这场艳遇
because he was really looking forward to this!
宾  快看那对双胞胎姐妹一起跳舞
Bing! Look at those twin sisters dancing together.
我出钱请她们在你大腿上跳艳舞吧
Let me buy you a lap dance with those girls.
不用了  而且只有一个女孩在跳舞
That's all right, sir. And that's just one girl.
宾  这是什么  那是我的手
Bing, what's this?  It's a hand.
用来帮你端酒的工具
It's a thing you use as a Jack and Coke holder.
不  是婚戒  你得把它丢掉
No. It's a wedding ring. You gotta get rid of it.
我们现在就到东河把它扔下去
We're gonna go to the East River right now and throw it in there!
不要  要
No!  Yes!
我就那么做了  感觉好很多
I did it, and I felt a lot better!
如果你仍得有准头  甚至可能会打中海鸥
And if you whip it just right you might hit a seagull in the head.
好吧  我需要一堆备用钥匙
Okay. I'm gonna need a bunch of extra keys.
很明显  我会毫无理由地把钥匙送人
Apparently, I give them away for no reason at all.
罗斯  发生了什么事  你在换锁
Ross, what's going on? You're changing the lock?
不是
No.
是那个家伙在换锁
That guy is.
我这就不懂了  你刚把你家的钥匙给我
I don't understand. You give me a key to your apartment,
然后你就把锁换了
and then you change the lock?
祝你好运  哥们
Good luck, buddy.
我以为我们往前迈进了一步
I thought we were moving forward.
而现在你却向我发送各种混乱讯息
Now you're sending me all these mixed signals.
你到底想告诉我什么
What are you trying to tell me?
我想告诉你...
I'm trying to tell you...
我帮你录了一卷集锦录音带
...I made you a mix tape.
什么  我爱你
What?  I love you.
我喜欢跟你在一起
And I love spending time with you.
老婆  我回来了
Hi, honey, I'm home.
从龙舌兰酒工厂回来的
From the tequila factory?
感觉糟透了
It was awful.
为了逃避跟道格的晚餐约会
To get out of going to dinner with Doug,
我告诉他你跟我分居了
I told him you and I split up.
他拖我去脱衣舞俱乐部  还有色情酒吧
So then he took me to these strip clubs and sleazy bars.
我不肯把婚戒交给他
When I wouldn't give him my wedding ring,
他就用汽水罐打小鸟
he threw a soda can at a bird.
过来  我可以用嘴巴呼吸
Come here. I can breathe through my mouth.
亲爱的  你知道最糟糕的是什么吗
Oh, sweetie. You know what the worst part was?
我预见到了没有你的生活是什么样子
I got to see what my life would be like without you.
就像是《生活多美好》配上艳舞
It was like It's a Wonderful Life with lap dances.
请答应我  你永远不会离开我
Please promise me that you'll never leave me...
我们会一起变老
...that we'll grow old together,
相伴一生
and be with each other for the rest of our lives.
我答应你
I promise.
说到相伴一生
Speaking of together,
我们今年一起寄节日贺卡吧
how about we send out a holiday card this year?
我不知道我们是不是到那个地步了
I don't know if we're there yet.
我想订披萨  我能问你一个问题吗
I'd like to order a pizza. Can I ask you a question?
今晚是那个金发帅哥外送吗
Is the cute blond guy delivering tonight?
长得又酷又时髦的那个
Very "Abercrombie & Fitch."
我再打给你  你在跟谁打电话
I'll call you back.  Who was that?
我在订披萨
It's just the pizza place.
你竟然挂掉了订披萨的电话
You hung up on the pizza place?
我可不会挂掉你朋友的电话
I don't hang up on your friends.
抱歉  今天我过得不顺心
Sorry, honey, I'm just having a rough day.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你不会想听的
You don't want to hear about it.
不然我为什么要问
Then why did I ask?
这真的很丢脸
Okay, this is really embarrassing,
但最近自从我怀孕后
but lately, with this whole pregnancy thing...
我发现自己...
...I'm just finding myself...
我该怎么说呢
How do I put this?
春情大发
Erotically charged.
那是"性饥渴"的学名吗
Is that college talk for "horny"?
对  我心中充满了欲望
Yeah. I have all of these feelings,
但却不知道该怎么处理
and I don't know what to do about them.
我没办法像正常人去约会
I can't date like a normal person,
这没关系  因为我不需要男朋友
which is fine because I don't need a relationship.
我只想要一夜情  只有性爱就好
All I really want is one great night! Just sex.
没有牵绊  不谈恋爱
No strings attached. No relationship.
就跟我喜欢的人在一起
With someone I feel comfortable with,
他懂得掌握分寸
and who knows what he's doing.
只要共度一夜春宵
For just one great night.
真的就那么难...
I mean, is that really so hard...
找到吗
...to find?
你今天过得如何
So how was your day?
很好  我看见一只超大的鸽子
Good. I saw a pretty big pigeon.
我还得早起  都快七点了
Well, I gotta get up early, and it's almost 7:00.
我得回房了  晚安
I gotta go to my room.  Good night!
晚安
Good night!
我不能那么做  我没有要你那么做
I can't do it!  I didn't ask you to do it!
你是瑞秋  你是乔伊
You're Rachel!  You're Joey!
你是我的朋友  你也是我的朋友
You're my friend!  Right back at you.
对  而且那样是不对的  怪异又恶劣
Yeah. Plus, it would be wrong, and weird and bad!
太恶劣了  但我不知道你在说什么
So bad! But I don't know what you're talking about.
因为我没要求你做什么事  我知道
Because I didn't ask you to do anything!  I know!
你想做吗  不想
You wanna do it?  No!
我也不想  我只是在考验你
Me neither. I'm just testing you!
那这件事就到此为止了
Well, that's the end of this conversation!
就当什么都没发生过  没错
This conversation never happened!  Never happened!
晚安  晚安
Good night!  Good night!
快回你房里
Get back in there!
听着  关于罗杰的事  我很抱歉
Listen, I'm sorry about that whole thing with Roger.
那么做很不合适  我想弥补你
It really wasn't right. And I want to make it up to you.
我带了一样我觉得你会喜欢的东西来
So I brought you something I think you'll really enjoy.
我只是借给你用  好吗
Now this is just a loan, okay?
我还会把它拿回去
I'm gonna want him back.
我得走了
I'm gonna go now.
抱歉  我以为我办得到  但却不行
I'm sorry. I thought I could do it, and I can't.